Guide to the Mandy Carter Papers, 1970-2013 RL.00195
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Gigs and Events Series, 1979-2013, 108 boxes
  - NBJC Board Call, 2006 June 16 (Box 189)
  - Southwest Social Forum, Durham, N.C., 2006 June 16-18 (Box 189)
  - Black-Latino Pride Week, Columbia, S.C., 2006 June 19-25 (Box 189)
  - Call to Justice Sunday, Charlotte, N.C., 2006 June 25 (Box 190)
  - Meeting wih Barbara Lau, Durham, N.C., 2006 June 26 (Box 190)
  - Camping with Keeling and Chandra, Hanging Rock State Park, N.C., 2006 July 8-9 (Box 190)
  - AFFA Meeting, Charleston, S.C., 2006 July 11 (Box 190)
  - Meeting with Ken, Charleston, S.C., 2006 July 12 (Box 190)
  - Silver Roses Meeting, Raleigh, N.C., 2006 July 16 (Box 190)
  - Visit with Lorraine & Bev, Durham, N.C., 2006 July 16, 2 folders (Box 190)
  - 2006 Charlotte Black Pride, Charlotte, N.C., 2006 July 20-23 (Box 190)
  - Beach Visit with Laurie & Lynette, Myrtle Beach, S.C., 2006 July 24-25 (Box 190)
  - Intergenerational Think Tank, Highlander, Tenn., 2006 July 27-30 (Box 190)
  - 2006 NABWMT Convention, Long Beach, Calif., 2006 July 31-Aug. 5 (Box 190)
  - Black LGBT Meeting Juan Battle, Montreal, Canada, 2006 Aug. 11 (Box 190)
  - SCEC Training Summit, Columbia, S.C., 2006 Aug. 19-20 (Box 190)
  - OLOC Host Committee Wrap-up Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2006 Aug. 29 (Box 190)
  - 11th Landdyke Gathering, West Wind, Ribera, N.M., 2006 Sept. 2-8 (Box 190)
  - Neighborhood Funders Group Conference, Durham, N.C., 2006 Sept. 11-13 (Box 190)
  - SWOOP Strong Women and Heroes Dinner, Durham, N.C., 2006 Sept. 16 (Box 190)
  - "A Call to Men" Domestic Violence, N.C., 2006 Sept. 20-22 (Box 190)
  - 1st SONG Think Tank, Highlander Center, New Market, Tenn., 2006 Sept. 22-24 (Box 190)
  - UNC GLBT-SA Retreat, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2006 Sept. 23 (Box 190)
  - Katrina Neighbors Solidarity Tour Planning Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2006 Sept. 26 (Box 190)
  - Bill Golida Planning Meeting for 2007, San Francisco, Calif., 2006 Sept. (Box 190)
  - Visit to Coya Artichoker SCEC, Columbia, S.C., 2006 Oct. 3, 2 folders (Box 190)
  - SONG Fall Campout, Roan Mountain, Tenn., 2006 Oct. 6-8 (Box 190)
  - SCEC Meeting, Orangeburg, S.C., 2006 Oct. 9, 2 folders (Box 190)
  - Fayetteville NOW Meeting, Fayetteville, N.C., 2006 Oct. 11 (Box 191)
  - All Families Matter Tour, Columbia, S.C., 2006 Oct. 17 (Box 191)
  - All Families Matter Tour, Orangeburg, S.C., 2006 Oct. 18 (Box 191)
  - All Families Matter Tour, Charleston, S.C., 2006 Oct. 19 (Box 191)
  - All Families Matter Tour, Charleston, S.C. to Durham, N.C., 2006 Oct. 20 (Box 191)
  - SCEC GoTV Training of Trainers, Columbia, S.C., 2006 Nov. 4 (Box 191)
  - CC 2006, Kansas City, Mo., 2006 Nov. 7-12, 8 folders (Box 191)
  - Harriet Hancock's 70th Birthday Roast/Dinner, Columbia, S.C., 2006 Nov. 18 (Box 191)
  - SONG 2nd Think Tank, Nauvoo, Ala., 2006 Dec. 8-10 (Box 191)
  - 2007 Stuff (Box 192)
  - Highlander, New Market, Tenn., 2007 Jan. (Box 192)
  - Durham YMCA, Durham, N.C., 2007 Jan. 3 (Box 192)
  - NCPJ Meeting & Potluck, Knightdale, N.C., 2007 Jan. 7 (Box 192)
  - Holmes Hummel Potluck, Durham, N.C., 2007 Jan. 10 (Box 192)
  - SONG Training with Paulina and Caitlin, Durham, N.C., 2007 Jan. 11 (Box 192)
  - 2nd Fayetteville BRCA, Fayetteville, N.C., 2007 Jan. 13 (Box 192)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2007 Jan. 14 (Box 192)
  - Meeting with Joyce of NCOSH, Durham, N.C., 2007 Jan. 19 (Box 192)
  - WRL Screening "Brother Outsider," New York, N.Y., 2007 Jan. 19 (Box 192)
  - Drive to Tennessee, Knoxville, Tenn., 2007 Jan. 20 (Box 192)
  - SONG House Party, Knoxville, Tenn., 2007 Jan. 21 (Box 192)
  - Duke vs. Tennessee, Knoxville, Tenn., 2007 Jan. 22 (Box 192)
  - Alexis "Listening session," Durham, N.C., 2007 Jan. 24 (Box 192)
  - Informal Dinner 1st one, Durham, N.C., 2007 Jan. 24 (Box 192)
  - Dinner with Sam, Kristi, Shannon, Durham, N.C., 2007 Jan. 25 (Box 192)
  - March on Washington, UFPJ, Washington, D.C., 2007 Jan. 27 (Box 192)
  - Bridgette Burge Heirs Interview, Durham, N.C., 2007 Feb. 2 (Box 192)
  - LGBT Democrats 2nd Salon, Washington, D.C., 2007 Feb. 5 (Box 192)
  - Meeting with Terah re: Shaw St. Aug, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2007 Feb. 7 (Box 192)
  - 2nd Visit Kelly re: My Papers, Durham, N.C., 2007 Feb. 8 (Box 192)
  - 2007 UU's Interweave Convo, Atlanta, Ga., 2007 Feb. 9-11, 2 folders (Box 192)
  - Justice or Just Us Workshop, Atlanta, Ga., 2007 Feb. 10 (Box 192)
  - Meeting with Simone LLDEF, Atlanta, Ga., 2007 Feb. 10 (Box 192)
  - Meeting with Shannon, Durham, N.C., 2007 Feb. 12 (Box 192)
  - University of MN @ Duluth, Duluth, Minn., 2007 Feb. 13-15 (Box 192)
  - Outfront Minnesota, Minneapolis, Minn., 2007 Feb. 16 (Box 192)
  - Alphabet Soup 2007, Midwest Bisexual Lesbian Gay Transgender Ally College, Minneapolis, Minn., 2006 Feb. 16-18 (Box 192)
  - Midwest GLBTA 2007 Conference, Minneapolis, Minn., 2007 Feb. 16-19 (Box 193)
  - Soul Essence Event, Minneapolis, Minn., 2007 Feb. 18 (Box 193)
  - Charlotte Business Guild, Charlotte, N.C., 2007 Feb. 20 (Box 193)
  - FLGI Teleconference Call, 2007 Mar. 1 (Box 193)
  - 2007 Women's ACC, Greensboro, N.C., 2007 Mar. 1-4 (Box 193)
  - Peaceworks Interview, 2007 Mar. 6 (Box 193)
  - North Carolina Women United Planning Meeting, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2007 Mar. 6 (Box 193)
  - NBJC Black Church Summit 2007, Philadelphia, Pa., 2007 Mar. 10 (Box 193)
  - Beyond Boundaries: A Blueprint for LGBTI Healthcare Equality, Philadelphia, Pa., 2007 Mar. 14-18 (Box 193)
  - Eric Rofes Tribute, Philadelphia, Pa., 2007 Mar. 15 (Box 193)
  - Black LGBTI Health Issues Plenary BGMLC Reception, Philadelphia, Pa., 2007 Mar. 16 (Box 193)
  - 4th March on Fayetteville, Fayetteville, N.C., 2007 Mar. 17 (Box 193)
  - Dinner with Bill Towe, Raleigh, N.C., 2007 Mar. 21 (Box 193)
  - "Sexual Identities with Racial Difference in 20th Century," Atlanta, Ga., 2007 Mar. 26 (Box 193)
  - Emory Human Rights Week Keynote, Atlanta, Ga., 2007 Mar. 26 (Box 193)
  - 3rd Dinner Out, Durham, N.C., 2007 Mar. 27 (Box 193)
  - UNC Southern Oral History Class, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2007 Mar. 28 (Box 193)
  - NCWU Diversity/Values Board Retreat, 2007 Mar. 31 (Box 193)
  - SONG Camp Out, Jacksonville, Fla., 2007 Apr. 6-8 (Box 194)
  - Duke Packing Days, Durham, N.C., 2007 Apr. 9-11, 3 folders (Box 194)
  - SONG Meeting, New Market, Tenn., 2007 Apr. 13-15 (Box 194)
  - Jordan High School GSA, Durham, N.C., 2007 Apr. 17 (Box 194)
  - Duke Allies Lecture, Durham, N.C., 2007 Apr. 20 (Box 194)
  - Beach Trip 2007, Nags Head, N.C., 2007 Apr. 21-28 (Box 194)
  - 2nd Annual UNC Chapel Hill Lavender Graduation, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2007 Apr. 28 (Box 194)
  - SF Trip, San Francisco, Calif., 2007 May 7-22, 2 folders (Box 194)
  - National Center for Lesbian Rights 30th Anniversary Gala, San Francisco, Calif., 2007 May 11-13 (Box 194)
  - 40th Annivesary Bill Gonda Visit to Palo Alto, Palo Alto, Calif., 2007 May 14 (Box 194)
  - North Carolina Women United Board Meeting, 2007 May 23 (Box 194)
  - AJ Taylor Play, S.C., 2007 June (Box 194)
  - 2nd Annual Faithful Call to Justice, 2007 June 2-3 (Box 194)
  - Lunch with Cal and Mike, Durham, N.C., 2007 June 5 (Box 194)
  - Women for Hillary Block Party, Washington, D.C., 2007 June 6 (Box 194)
  - Center for Documentary Studies, Durham, N.C., 2007 June 19 (Box 194)
  - Durham Rising-Drag Bingo, Durham, N.C., 2007 June 24 (Box 194)
  - Housing at Everettes/SONG Cookout, Atlanta, Ga., 2007 June 25-26 (Box 194)
  - Building a Queer Left: Pre-USSF Gathering, Atlanta, Ga., 2007 June 26 (Box 194)
  - US Social Forum, Atlanta, Ga., 2007 June 27-July 1, 2 folders (Box 195)
  - WRL Southern Listening Project, Triangle Area, N.C., 2007 July 2-3, 5-7 (Box 195)
  - Pre CDs Video Institute Meeting with Mayme, Durham, N.C., 2007 July 11 (Box 195)
  - Meeting with Ronna re: Out & Equal, Durham, N.C., 2007 July 12 (Box 195)
  - Germaine Curtain's Cabin, Schnectady, N.Y., 2007 July 16-17 (Box 195)
  - Word & World Mini-School, Smithfield, N.C., 2007 July 19, 2 folders (Box 195)
  - 3rd Annual Charlotte Black Prdie, Charlotte, N.C., 2007 July 21 (Box 195)
  - Hanging with Hillary Party, Durham, N.C., 2007 July 23 (Box 195)
  - Quality of Life Revisualization Planning, Durham, N.C., 2007 July 25, 2 folders (Box 195)
  - Milo Interview, Durham, N.C., 2007 July 30 (Box 195)
  - Durham Human Relations Unity Conference, Durham, N.C., 2007 Aug. 11 (Box 196)
  - Phat Queer Youth Planning Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2007 Aug. 12 (Box 196)
  - Duke LGBT Center Program, Durham, N.C., 2007 Aug. 28 (Box 196)
  - Han Johnson Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2007 Aug. 29 (Box 196)
  - Duffy Baum Visit, Durham, N.C., 2007 Aug. 30 (Box 196)
  - 75th Anniversary Highlander, New Market, Tenn., 2007 Aug. 31-Sept. 2, 2 folders (Box 196)
  - Lillian's List Tribute to Jeanne Lucas, Durham, N.C., 2007 Sept. 5 (Box 196)
  - 1st Conference Call-Haas Re: April 23-24, 2008 Black Ministers Meeting, 2007 Sept. 6 (Box 196)
  - Molly Chadborne Interview, Durham, N.C., 2007 Sept. 7 (Box 196)
  - September 15 Act Now To Stop War and End Racism (ANSWER) Demo, Washington, D.C., 2007 Sept. 15 (Box 196)
  - Feminist Majority--From Campus to Congres: Women of Color Creating Change, Greensboro, N.C., 2007 Sept. 22, 2 folders (Box 196)
  - Tes's Fall Equinox Party, 2007 Sept. 22 (Box 196)
  - Randy Miller/Haas Call, 2007 Sept. 24 (Box 196)
  - Durham Democratic Women Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2007 Sept. 24 (Box 196)
  - Durham City Council-Majority Forum, Durham, N.C., 2007 Sept. 25 (Box 196)
  - NBJC RAC Call, 2007 Sept. 26 (Box 196)
  - ZAMI Audre Lorde Scholarships, Atlanta, Ga., 2007 Sept. 28-29 (Box 196)
  - Evelyn and Walter Haas, Jr. Fund Files, 2007 Oct., 7 folders (Box 197)
  - Durham Board of Elections Precinct 8 Training, Durham, N.C., 2007 Oct. 1 (Box 197)
  - Durham Quality of Life Durham Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2007 Oct. 1 (Box 197)
  - Durham Change Conference Barnard College, New York, N.Y., 2007 Oct. 4-7 (Box 197)
  - SWOOP Award Dinner, Durham, N.C., 2007 Oct. 6 (Box 197)
  - Durham Primary Election Poll Workers, Durham, N.C., 2007 Oct. 9 (Box 197)
  - Resist 4th Anniversary Panel, Boston, Mass., 2007 Oct. 13 (Box 197)
  - Brunch-Reunion, Cambridge, Mass., 2007 Oct. 14 (Box 197)
  - Auction-on-line (Box 197)
  - Haas Call Re: Black Church Summit, 2007 Oct. 16 (Box 197)
  - Ohio University, Athens, Ohio, 2007 Oct. 17-19, 2 folders (Box 197)
  - Reversing the Retreat on Civil Rights, Durham, N.C., 2007 Oct. 19-20, 2 folders (Box 197)
  - Why We Can't Wait: Reversing the Retreat on Civil Rights, Durham, N.C., 2007 Oct. 19-20 (Box 198)
  - Teleconference Call-Haas, Durham, N.C., 2007 Oct. 24 (Box 198)
  - Gill Foundation--African American Leadership Gathering, Denver, Colo., 2007 Oct. 25-28, 2 folders (Box 198)
  - Gill Foundation/Black Leadership Meeting-Strategy Session, Denver, Colo., 2007 Oct. 25-28 (Box 198)
  - Creating Change 2007 Adoption Workshops, Detroit, Mich., 2007 Nov. (Box 198)
  - Lillian's List 10th Anniversary Gala, Cary, N.C., 2007 Nov. 2 (Box 198)
  - Equality NC Conference, Durham, N.C., 2007 Nov. 3, 2 folders (Box 198)
  - Durham City-County Primary Election-Precint 8, Durham, N.C., 2007 Nov. 6 (Box 198)
  - Technology of Participation® Facilitation Training, Greensboro, N.C., 2007 Nov. 7-8 (Box 199)
  - Fayetteville NOW Meeting, Fayetteville, N.C., 2007 Nov. 14 (Box 199)
  - Joe Herzenberg Memorial, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2007 Nov. 15 (Box 199)
  - Tennessee vs. Texas, Knoxville, Tenn., 2007 Nov. 18 (Box 199)
  - Progressive Democrats of North Carolina Annual Meeting, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2007 Dec. 8 (Box 199)
  - Durham Community Land Trust Annual Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2007 Dec. 10 (Box 199)
  - Michael Dolan Fliss Visit, Hillsborough, N.C., 2007 Dec. 10 (Box 199)
  - Durham County Democratic Women, Durham, N.C., 2007 Dec. 11 (Box 199)
  - Cultural Committee Call-1st, 2007 Dec. 12 (Box 199)
  - Hillary Clinton for President, 2008 (Box 199)
  - Durham Democratic Women Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Jan. 2 (Box 199)
  - Get Together With Mike-Cal-Me, Hillsborough, N.C., 2008 Jan. 4 (Box 199)
  - 2nd Cultural Committee Call, 2008 Jan. 9 (Box 199)
  - Heirs Project & Church of Reconciliation, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2008 Jan. 10 (Box 199)
  - Haas Call, 2008 Jan. 22 (Box 199)
  - NBJC RAC Call 11 am EST, 2008 Jan. 23 (Box 199)
  - 3-Way Call Phillip-Pauline Re: CC 2008 Adoption/Foster Workshops, 2008 Jan. 23 (Box 199)
  - UMN-Duluth BRCA, Duluth, Minn., 2008 Jan. 26 (Box 199)
  - NC Democratic Party State Executive Committee, Hamlet, N.C., 2008 Jan. 26 (Box 199)
  - January PDNC Meeting 10 AM, Hamlet, N.C., 2008 Jan. 26 (Box 199)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Jan. 29 (Box 199)
  - AALG Cultural Committee Call, 2008 Jan. 30 (Box 199)
  - WUNC "State of Things" Show, 2008 Jan. 30 (Box 199)
  - Durham Raucous Caucus, Durham, N.C., 2008 Jan. 30 (Box 199)
  - SONG 15th Anniversary Planning Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Feb. 1 (Box 199)
  - 3rd Annual Fayetteville BRCA, Fayetteville, N.C., 2008 Feb. 2 (Box 199)
  - Creating Change 2008, Detroit, Mich., 2008 Feb. 6-10, 12 folders (Box 199-200)
  - Durham Dem Women Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Feb. 12 (Box 200)
  - 2nd SONG 15th Anniversary Committee Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Feb. 13 (Box 200)
  - Susan B. Anthony event, Fayetteville NOW, Fayetteville, N.C., 2008 Feb. 15 (Box 200)
  - Jim Neal "Meet & Greet", Hillsborough, N.C., 2008 Feb. 17 (Box 200)
  - Equality NC 2009 Planning Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Feb. 20 (Box 200)
  - Mark Herzog Dinner-Meeting, Carrboro, N.C., 2008 Feb. 20 (Box 200)
  - David Kerley-NCAARP Call, 2008 Feb. 21 (Box 200)
  - Latino Issues in Durham & NC, Durham, N.C., 2008 Feb. 21 (Box 200)
  - Lunch Meeting Stacey Cray, Durham, N.C., 2008 Feb. 21 (Box 200)
  - Randall Call, 2008 HAAS Contract LBJ, 2008 Feb. 22 (Box 200)
  - Dinner OUT, Durham, N.C., 2008 Feb. 25 (Box 200)
  - Meeting at Jim Neal for US Senate Office, Durham, N.C., 2008 Feb. 27 (Box 200)
  - Janie Long Class @ LGBT Center, Duke University, Durham, N.C., 2008 Feb. 28 (Box 200)
  - NC Public Allies Hetersexism Panel, Durham, N.C., 2008 Feb. 29 (Box 200)
  - Windcall Conference Call re: Susan Williams, 2008 Feb. 29 (Box 200)
  - Durham County for Hillary, 2008 Mar.-Apr. (Box 200)
  - Hillary, North Carolina, 2008 Mar.-May (Box 200)
  - Heir Project Retreat, Mebane, N.C., 2008 Mar. 1 (Box 200)
  - 1st Tuesday Durham Dem Women, Durham, N.C., 2008 Mar. 4 (Box 200)
  - NCSU Gig, Raleigh, N.C., 2008 Mar. 5 (Box 201)
  - Precinct 08 Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Mar. 11 (Box 201)
  - SONG 15th Anniversary Planning Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Mar. 12 (Box 201)
  - March Dinner OUT, Durham, N.C., 2008 Mar. 13 (Box 201)
  - Carolina Black Pride Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Mar. 15 (Box 201)
  - Jim Neal Briefing Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Mar. 17 (Box 201)
  - Pro-Choice K/O Men for Neal, Carrboro, N.C., 2008 Mar. 18 (Box 201)
  - Voter Registration @ Duke Hosp., Durham, N.C., 2008 Mar. 20 (Box 201)
  - NC AARP Meeting, Raleigh, N.C., 2008 Mar. 20 (Box 201)
  - NC for Hillary, Goldsboro, N.C., 2008 Mar. 21 (Box 201)
  - UNC Women's Week Panel, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2008 Mar. 25 (Box 201)
  - 2nd ENC Summit Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Mar. 26 (Box 201)
  - Jim Neal-Kay Hagan Debate, New Bern, N.C., 2008 Mar. 28 (Box 201)
  - SONG Campout, Fort Mountain State Park, Chatsworth, Ga., 2008 Mar. 28-30 (Box 201)
  - Susan & Albee Miller Windcall Book Stop, Durham, N.C., 2008 Mar. 30 (Box 201)
  - Robyn Ochs & ECU, Greenville, N.C., 2008 Apr. 3 (Box 201)
  - Kari Point Hook-Up, 2008 Apr. 5 (Box 201)
  - Unity Conference 2008, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2008 Apr. 4-6 (Box 201)
  - Hillary Meeting with Cathy Moore, Durham, N.C., 2008 Apr. 6 (Box 201)
  - Terri's Health Care Professionals Class on LGBT and Ally, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2008 Apr. 8 (Box 201)
  - May 3 Precinct Block Party Mtg, Durham, N.C., 2008 Apr. 8 (Box 201)
  - Chris Stewart, Hillary Clinton Fundraiser, Goldsboro, N.C., 2008 Apr. 8-10 (Box 202)
  - People's Alliance Endorsement Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Apr. 9 (Box 201)
  - Hillary Burlington Office Opening, Graham, N.C., 2008 Apr. 10 (Box 201)
  - Randall Miller-Haas Contract Call, Durham, N.C., 2008 Apr. 11 (Box 201)
  - UNC-G Safe Zone Training Keynote, Greensboro, N.C., 2008 Apr. 11 (Box 201)
  - "Love Welcomes All" Conference, Hendersonville, N.C., 2008 Apr. 12 (Box 201)
  - UU Fellowship Hendersonville, Hendersonville, N.C., 2008 Apr. 13 (Box 201)
  - Solidarity & Sanity Dinner, Durham, N.C., 2008 Apr. 13 (Box 201)
  - Marcie's School of Social Work Class, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2008 Apr. 14 (Box 201)
  - HAAS Interview with Harry Knox, 2008 Apr. 15 (Box 201)
  - Brandeis University, Waltham, Mass., 2008 Apr. 16-18 (Box 202)
  - Black Latino Pre-Meeting Conference Call, 2008 Apr. 18 (Box 202)
  - Durham Board of Elections Training, Durham, N.C., 2008 Apr. 19 (Box 202)
  - 2008 Beach Week, Nags Head, N.C., 2008 Apr. 19-26 (Box 202)
  - Center of Lesbian and Gay Studies in Religion and Ministry AA Meeting, Baltimore, Md., 2008 Apr. 23-24, 2 folders (Box 202)
  - NBJC Power of Us Conference, Baltimore, Md., 2008 Apr. 24-26, 6 folders (Box 202)
  - Black-Latino Meeting, Philadelphia, Pa., 2008 Apr. 25 (Box 202)
  - Dinner with Janie Long, Durham, N.C., 2008 Apr. 28 (Box 202)
  - Access to Education for Immigrant Students, Raleigh, N.C., 2008 Apr. 28 (Box 202)
  - Pct 08, 09, 10m 40 Fun Day, Durham, N.C., 2008 May 3 (Box 202)
  - Goldsboro Hillary Event, Goldsboro, N.C., 2008 May 3 (Box 202)
  - SONG'S Knoxville 15th Anniversary Event, Knoxville, Tenn., 2008 May 4 (Box 202)
  - NCLGBTA for Jim Neal, Durham, N.C., 2008 May 4, 2 folders (Box 202)
  - NC Primary Election Day, Durham, N.C., 2008 May 6 (Box 202)
  - May Durham Dem Women Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 May 6 (Box 202)
  - B.A.R. Interview Re: Jim Neal, 2008 May 7 (Box 202)
  - Jean Kosofsky Lunch Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 May 8 (Box 202)
  - Molly Chadbourne Breakfast Meeting re: Ladyslipper Thesis, Durham, N.C., 2008 May 15 (Box 202)
  - Training Out & Equal Social Info Mtg, Durham, N.C., 2008 May 15 (Box 202)
  - 4th Congressional District Convention, Raleigh, N.C., 2008 May 17 (Box 203)
  - SONG 15th Anniversary Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 May 21 (Box 203)
  - DC Black Pride 2008, Washington, D.C., 2008 May 25 (Box 203)
  - LLDEF, Lawrence v. Texas, Washington, D.C., 2008 June 5 (Box 203)
  - Beaver Queen Pageant, Durham, N.C., 2008 June 7 (Box 203)
  - SONG Campout, Tyco, Va., 2008 June 13-15 (Box 203)
  - Hilllary Supporters Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 June 18 (Box 203)
  - Independent Photo Shoot with Jim Neal, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2008 June 19 (Box 203)
  - Triangle Black Pride Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 June 21 (Box 203)
  - WRL Organizers Training, Voluntown, Conn., 2008 June 22-24 (Box 203)
  - Interview with Phil Gambohe, Voluntown, Conn., 2008 June 25 (Box 203)
  - Diane Sabin,Lesbian Health & Research Center National Advisory Council Meeting, San Francisco, Calif., 2008 June 27-28 (Box 203)
  - Susan Fahey, San Francisco, Calif., 2008 June 27-July 6 (Box 203)
  - 2008 SF Trip (Maud's Reunion Meeting, IDEAS), San Francisco, Calif., 2008 June 27-July 6 (Box 203)
  - Get Together With My Friends, San Francisco, Calif., 2008 June 30-July 2 (Box 203)
  - Meeting with Randy Miller, San Francisco, Calif., 2008 July 1 (Box 203)
  - National Black Lesbian Conference, Las Vegas, Nev., 2008 July 10-13, 3 folders (Box 203)
  - Neighborhood Watch Meeting, PAC 3, Durham, N.C., 2008 July 16 (Box 204)
  - SONG Videotaping, Durham, N.C., 2008 July 17 (Box 204)
  - Diamond Affair, Atlanta, Ga., 2008 July 18 (Box 204)
  - Lunch meeting with Matt Smucker, Durham, N.C., 2008 July 22 (Box 204)
  - Photos to Jon Frankel, 2008 July 25 (Box 204)
  - Durham Obama Office Opening, Durham, N.C., 2008 July 26 (Box 204)
  - Triangle Black Pride Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Aug. 2 (Box 204)
  - SAF End of Summer Celebration, Durham, N.C., 2008 Aug. 8 (Box 204)
  - PAC 3 Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Aug. 9 (Box 204)
  - ENC Planning Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Aug. 13 (Box 204)
  - Obama Pride Table at NCLGTF, Durham, N.C., 2008 Aug. 14-17 (Box 204)
  - 2nd Durham Obama Pride Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Aug. 15 (Box 204)
  - Greensboro SONG Event, Greensboro, N.C., 2008 Aug. 16 (Box 204)
  - Heirs Project Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Aug. 19 (Box 204)
  - Dinner & Priscilla and Annie's, Durham, N.C., 2008 Aug. 20 (Box 204)
  - Obama Acceptance Speech Watch Party & Rally, Durham, N.C., 2008 Aug. 28 (Box 204)
  - Immigrant Issues Strategy Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Aug. 29 (Box 204)
  - Obama Surrogate Atlanta Black Pride Town Meeting, Atlanta, Ga., 2008 Aug. 30 (Box 204)
  - Obama Pride Canvas & Voter Reformation, Atlanta, Ga., 2008 Aug. 31 (Box 204)
  - Victory Church Services, Stone Mountain, Ga., 2008 Aug. 31 (Box 204)
  - Julie Meeting with Woman South Boston, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2008 Sept. 3 (Box 204)
  - SONG Annivesary Planning Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Sept. 3 (Box 204)
  - Durham for Obama Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Sept. 5 (Box 204)
  - Triangle Feminist--Take Back White House, Durham, N.C., 2008 Sept. 6 (Box 204)
  - Eleven Women First Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2008 Sept. 8 (Box 204)
  - South Carolina Equality Coalition Town Meeting, Columbia, S.C., 2008 Sept. 18 (Box 204)
  - Breakfast with Rev. Colclough, Columbia, S.C., 2008 Sept. 19 (Box 204)
  - SONG's 15th Annivesary Weekend, Durham, N.C., 2008 Sept. 19-21, 2 folders (Box 205)
  - SC Pride 2008, Columbia, S.C., 2008 Sept. 20 (Box 205)
  - 1st Social Justice Symposium UNC-Pembroke, Pembroke, N.C., 2008 Sept. 22 (Box 205)
  - Anaré Holmes Radio Interview, 2008 Sept. 23 (Box 205)
  - ZAMI Audre Lorde Scholarships, Atlanta, Ga., 2008 Sept. 26-27 (Box 205)
  - NC Pridefest 2008, Durham, N.C., 2008 Sept. 27 (Box 205)
  - George Morgan Meeting, Atlanta, Ga., 2008 Sept. 28 (Box 205)
  - Barbara Lau's Class, Durham, N.C., 2008 Sept. 29 (Box 205)
  - Holly Near in Washington, D.C., What's Happening?, Washington, D.C., 2008 Oct. 2 (Box 205)
  - Black-Brown Summitt, Dallas Black Pride, Dallas, Tex., 2008 Oct. 2-3 (Box 205)
  - UNC-Chapel Hill NCOD Talk, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2008 Oct. 7 (Box 205)
  - Jane Kniffin, People of Faith for Just Relationships Retreat, Asheville, N.C., 2008 Oct. 9 (Box 205)
  - Tyrone Greelee, Christians for a United Community Meeting, Asheville, N.C., 2008 Oct. 10 (Box 205)
  - Jane Kniffin, Commission to Defeat Racism Retreat, Asheville, N.C., 2008 Oct. 11 (Box 205)
  - UC Davis National Coming Out Week, Davis, Calif., 2008 Oct. 12-14 (Box 205)
  - UC Davis BRCA Meeting Intergenerational Panel, Davis, Calif., 2008 Oct. 13 (Box 205)
  - UC Davis Keynote, Davis, Calif., 2008 Oct. 13 (Box 205)
  - St. Cloud National Coming Out Week, St. Cloud, Minn., 2008 Oct. 20-22, 2 folders (Box 205)
  - 2008 General Election Training, Durham, N.C., 2008 Oct. 24 (Box 205)
  - NC Conference on Aging, AARP, Greenville, N.C., 2008 Oct. 28 (Box 206)
  - Intersections of Race & Sexuality, New York, N.Y., 2008 Nov. 6-7 (Box 206)
  - Russell Herman Fundraisers, Raleigh, Durham, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2008 Nov. 9-11 (Box 206)
  - Define This, Young Women of Color Creating Change, Bennett College, Greensboro, N.C., 2008 Nov. 14-15 (Box 206)
  - 2008 Equality NC Conference & Gala, Durham, N.C., 2008 Nov. 15, 2 folders (Box 206)
  - Russell Herman Durham Fundraiser, Durham, N.C., 2008 Nov. 16 (Box 206)
  - Highlander Southern Strategies III, New Market, Tenn., 2008 Nov. 18-20 (Box 206)
  - GLLI Session, Obama/Biden Transition, Washington, D.C., 2008 Dec. 4 (Box 206)
  - 2008 Progressive Democrats of North Carolina Conference, Greensboro, N.C., 2008 Dec. 6 (Box 206)
  - LGBTQQI Evening at Summit, Greensboro, N.C., 2008 Dec. 6 (Box 207)
  - SONG Office Move to Atlanta, Durham, N.C., 2008 Dec. 9-12 (Box 207)
  - National LGBT Meeting, Presidential Transition, Washington, D.C., 2008 Dec. 10 (Box 207)